(鬼屋)
∮ Dolly'll never go away Dolly'll never go away ∮
∮ 莉莉不会离去  莉莉不会离去 ∮
∮ Dolly'll never go away again ∮
∮ 莉莉永不再离去 ∮
Hey, do you guys know this one?
你知道这首吗
Now this is the real shit.
这首才劲爆
∮ Shake your ass, watch yourself ∮
∮ 摇摇你的屁屁  小心点 ∮
∮ Shake your ass Show me what you're working with ∮
∮ 让我看看你动感的身躯 ∮
∮ Attention all young players ∮
∮ 嫖客和皮条客 ∮
∮ and pimps Right now is the place to be ∮
∮ 快来干活 ∮
∮ I thought I told y'all niggers before ∮
∮ 我早警告过黑鬼 ∮
∮ Y'all niggers don't fuck with me ∮
∮ 别想搞上我 ∮
∮ Shake your ass Watch yourself ∮
∮ 摇摇你的屁屁  小心点 ∮
∮ Shake your ass Show me what you're working with Shake your ass ∮
∮ 让我看看你动感的身躯 ∮
You suck.
你们有病
She's good.
叫伊第一名
She... she's been really sick.
她病了很久
Bad, bad, bad girl!
夭寿死囝仔
OK. That'll be $17.50.
一共是17块5毛
Hey, buddy! Hey, pay the fare.
嘿  付钱啊
I'm Father McFeely.
我是麦神父
I'm so glad you're here.
很高兴你能赶到
I came as fast as I could,
我尽量加快
but at my age...the little soldier needs a lot more thumping...
但这把年纪还真不易
before it starts pumping, if you know what I mean.
需要些时间
I do find, though, if I tickle my asshole...
先摸摸屁眼
just before I unleash the dog of war...
会有帮助
It's OK. I understand.
够了  我懂了
You know, because in the old days...
你知道
you know when you...
当你
How is she?
她好吗
- It's gotten worse, Father.  - Really?
- 糟透了  神父  - 真的吗
She won't eat, she won't talk.
她不吃也不发一语
The child won't even let me touch her.
甚至不肯让我碰她
Yes. Sometimes you have to give them candy.
有时你得拿糖果来诱拐
Father...
神父
the church sent me to assist you. I'm Father Harris.
教会派我协助你
- Hi.  - Hi.
- 你好  - 你好
Nice to see you.
我是哈神父
Would you like to see the girl?
想见见那女孩吗
Soon... but first I must bless this house.
等会  我要先为这房子祈福
"The sorrows of death compassed me...
死亡的悲伤指引我
"and the pains of Hell got hold upon me. "I found..."
我背负地狱的苦痛
"Then called I upon the name of the Lord and..."
我大声呼喊上主之名
"My soul from death."
超脱我的灵魂
Oh, God. Please, Lord. Help me to release this demon.
神啊  请助我解除这恶魔
Thank you, Lord, the most merciful Almighty. Oh, hold on.
感谢上帝  仁慈万能的主
Ahh! Ah, those enchiladas. Ha ha ha!
噢  麻辣锅
Fuck this.
我不玩了
- Fuck! Did you see this?  - Look at this! Please,
- 你看到了吗  - 看看她  神父
- Father, think of the child.  - Fuck!
- 救救这孩子  - 妈的
Yes.
好吧
It's freezing.
好冷
Let us pray.
我们祈祷
"Defender of the human race... "look down in pity upon this, your servant."
人类的护卫者  请垂怜你的仆人
Shove it up your ass, you worthless piece of shit. Aah!
滚开  没用的老屁股
Silence!
闭嘴
"Holy Lord..."
全能的上帝
Your mother is in here with us, Harris.
小哈  你老妈也在这呢
Would you like to leave a message? I'll be sure that she gets it.
要留话吗  我会转告她
Yes. Mom, will you get out of there, please?
妈  你能不能出去
You're no fun.
你真无趣
I'm working.
我在工作
See you later, Mrs. Harris.
待会见了  哈妈妈
"Holy Lord, Almighty Father in..."
全能的上帝
"Everlasting God... "and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ...
不朽的天父  耶苏的老爸
"and the Virgin Mary's baby daddy.
圣母玛丽的小孩的老爸
"Holy Lord, Almighty Father... "everlasting God...
全能的上帝  不朽的天父
"who once consigned that fallen tyrant... "to the flames of Hell...
您曾将暴君打入炼狱
"who sent your only son into the world... "to crush that roaring tiger...
也曾派遣你儿子到尘世
"and who got that unholy bitch Jerri... "kicked off of "Survivor..."
也让作弊的人都被记大过
- Fuck me! Fuck me!  - Father!
- 上我  上我  - 神父
Father! This is not part of the ritual.
神父  没有人这样驱魔的
In the name of the Father, the Son, and the Holy...
以天父  基督之名
- Here you go, Father. All clean.  - Oh, thank you so much. OK.
- 拿着  神父  - 滚吧  谢谢你
You failed, McFeely. Your weapons are useless against me.
你的武器毫无作用
Let us pray.
我们祈祷
Our Father who Art in Heaven...
我们在天上的父啊
Stop it! Hallowed be Thy name.
住嘴  愿人都尊你的名
- Thy kingdom come.  - Your mother sucks cocks in Hell. Ha! Shit!
- 王国来临  - 闭嘴  你娘卡好
Suck on this.
好你的头
《惊声尖笑2》
(一年后)
So you think you made it into the class, Shorty?
矮子  你跟同学合得来吗
I sure hope so, Cindy.
算吧  辛蒂
You could use the grade, huh?
你需要用功点
Nah. I need a place to stay.
想要一个家
Mom Dukes kicked me out, but you know something?
却被老妈赶出门
I learned something very important in college...
但我在大学学到很重要的事
the value of books.
书的价值
Really?
真的
Yeah. Look at this here.
是啊  你看
Free paper. Ha ha! Shit, son.
卷烟纸
Yeah, so how you digging college?
你喜欢大学吗
I don't know. It's OK, I guess.
还好吧
I feel like such a geek sometimes, though.
但有时会觉得我好逊
Everyone is so cool, and I'm... not.
大家都很酷  我却很逊
Oh, come on, Cindy. You ain't that bad.
拜托  你也不赖啊
All you need is a little bit of flavor. Hmm. Maybe some new gear.
你只是需要点品味  加点料
"Gear?"
加料
That's slang for "clothing."
就是衣服
Here. Come on.We gonna cool you up right now.
来  现在就让你变酷
Don't sit like this, first of all. Don't sit like that, son. Sit cool.
首先  别这样坐
Right up, son. Feel yourself, son, like that.
要酷一点  大胆一点  放松  展现自我
Yeah. Now go like this. Uh. Uh, yeah.
好  接着这样
- That's cool.  - Yeah.
- 这就是酷  - 是啊
Yeah. Now stand up, let me show you some moves.
站起来  我教你几招
Right, left. Right, left. Uh, son. Uh!
右  左  右  左
Right, left. Right, kick. Uh, son. Uh, psych.
右  左  右  踢
Throw a little bit of slang in there.
接着嘴巴要说
Say, "Yo, that jacket is tight, son. Ya mean?"
外套不错嘛  痞子  拿来
Yo, that jacket is tight, son.
外套不错嘛  痞子
- Ya mean?  - Ya mean?
- 拿来  - 拿来
Yeah, something like that. Throw it all together.
就是这样  练一遍给我看
OK. Right, left. Right, kick, uh!
右  左  右  踢
Yo, that jacket is tight.
外套不错嘛
Now run that shit, bitch. Ya mean?
给我滚  贱货  拿来
That is the shit, dog.
正点
Oh, man. You boners aren't ready yet?
你们好了没
Dude, relax, man. I'm telling you, We'll get there on time, all right?
放心  我们不会迟到
Yo, dogs, what y'all think?
你们觉得怎样
Tucked in or out?
夹紧还是放开
- Out, man.  - Out, man.
- 哇靠  - 拜托
Come on. No doubt. No doubt. That's what I thought.
我想也是
You fuckheads would be ready if you weren't partying all night.
你们昨晚玩太疯了
Come on, man. It was so awesome. We got so wasted, man!
昨晚好棒  我真是爽呆了
I had, like, a keg myself. I woke up naked in a tub of ice.
我喝了一桶啤酒  醒来发现我裸体躺在一桶冰旁边
All right!
哇阿
Oh, shit, Ray, you got a tattoo.
小雷  你被刺青了
Oh, shit. What's it say?
靠  刺了什么
"Ray!" Oh, man.
小雷
Oh, shit, you got a tattoo, too.
靠  你也被刺青了
Oh, really? Dude! Dude, what's it say?
真的  刺了什么
"Fucked me."
搞我吧
Oh, sweet, man. "Ray..." "Fucked me." "Ray..." "Fucked me."
小雷  搞我吧  小雷  搞我吧
"Ray fucked me." Yeah! Ha ha! Whoo!
小雷  搞我吧
What, man?
什么
Wedgie moment! Ha ha!
来点刺激的吧
Come on. You're gonna give me a yeast infection.
拜托  别害我终身不举
- Hey, girl, that jacket is slamming.  - Thanks.
- 你外套真炫  - 谢谢
You better be careful, though.
小心点
Some girl got an ass-whipping... over a jacket stolen earlier today.
今天有人被攻击  还被抢了外套
Some people is so ghetto.
就是有人这么野蛮
What class we got next?
下节课是
Psychology.
心理学
Me, too! 101?
我也是  101室吗
-  In room 302 at 10:00?  -  That's it!
- 十点在302室  - 是的
Oh! Uh-uh! No. This is too much.
没错
I got these psychic powers on line.
真是的  我的第六感超强
Remind me to get a lotto ticket tomorrow. Oh, don't split the pole now.
明天记得提醒我去签六合彩  别分开走
That is very, very bad luck. My psychic told me.
第六感告诉我会带衰的
You don't really believe in that stuff, do you?
你不是真信那些吧
Yes, I do. Very much.
我信  我超信
(横行霸道请打投诉专线)
(鬼屋计划)
Are these all the subjects?
这些都是参加者
Yes, sir. I took the liberty of putting...
是的  最上面这些
those with near-death experiences on the very top.
都有濒死经验
Any of them hot?
有辣妹吗
As I'm sure you are aware, Professor...
我想你很清楚  教授
subjects who are close to death are
有濒死经验的人
statistically more likely to have the suggestibility required.
很适合用来做超自然调查
for paranormal investigation,
因此
which is why, of course, I gave them special consideration.
我特别考虑他们
Oh, good thinking, Dwight.
很好  歪头
Traumatized coeds are a sure thing.
受过伤的女学生最好搞
Ooh, I like her.
我喜欢她
Oh, yes, sir. That is Cindy Campbell...
是的  她是辛蒂
classic abandoned personality disorder.
典型的被遗弃型人格失序
She seems guarded, but willing.
她有防卫心  但很合作
And this?
这个呢
That is Ray Wilkins, sir. I couldn't quite figure him out.
那是小雷  我搞不清楚他
but he seemed very eager and pleased to meet me.
不过他见我时似乎很热情
What's this?
这是什么
It's a picture that he sent after the interview.
面谈后他寄给我的
Where did you find these kids?
你怎么找到他们的
Sir, they're all survivors of the Stevenston County Massacre.
他们都是史郡屠杀案的生还者
Oh, fantastic!
太好了
These kids are exactly the catalyst we need...
这些孩子就是最好的媒介
to awaken the spirits of Hell House.
可以唤醒鬼屋的恶灵
Sir, exactly how are we going to get them up there?
要如何骗他们过去
We'll tell them t's part of the class. We'll say, excuse me.
就说这是课程的一部分
that they're participating in a study of sleep disorders.
他们要参与睡眠失调的研究
We are going to make history, Dwight...
我们要成名了
the first documented...
第一篇有力的文献
unrefuted evidence of life after death.
窥探死后的生命
Welcome, everybody. I'm Professor Oldman.
各位好  我是欧教授
Each of you have been carefully selected to be in this class...
各位经过仔细的挑选
for which you receive an automatic grade of "A" upon completion.
将会自动获得优等成绩  只要完成研究
Now, this year's study is insomnia.
今年的研究主题是失眠
We are going to spend the weekend together...
我们要一起渡过一个周末
where we've established a controlled environment...
在受控制的环境下
in which we'll study your various sleep disorders.
一起研究各位的睡眠失调症
Now, I'll be passing out directions...
我会发给各位说明书
- I can do it.  - No, no, Dwight.
- 我可以发  - 不
I can do it.
我来发
I can... myself... do it.
我自己就能发
Now, you should all be there... by 6 p.m.
各位今晚六点要准时到达
Tonight and plan to stay through Monday.
要待到周一
I'll see you all this evening.
晚上见
- You left your book back there.  - Oh. Thanks.
- 你的书掉了  哈痢破特  - 谢谢
I'm Cindy.
我是辛蒂
- Buddy.  - Hey.
- 我是巴迪  - 你好
So, looks like we're gonna spend the weekend together.
看来我们要共度周末了
You want to get together and study or something?
要一起K书吗
Study? Ha!
K书
That was kind of bad.
算了
I'm sorry, Buddy. You seem like a really nice guy...
抱歉  巴迪  你人很好
but I just got out of a really bad relationship.
只是我刚结束一段恋情
so I'm not quite ready to start dating yet.
我还没准备好要再约会
But, hey, you know, maybe we could be friends.
也许我们能当朋友
Sure. Yeah. Cool. That... friends.
好  酷啊  当朋友
- OK. See you later, friend.  - All right, pal.
- 回头见了  朋友  - 好的  再见
Wedgie! Smell you later!
大内裤  回头见
As we go on we remember
我们活着  我们记得
All the good times We had together
我们曾共度美好时光
As our lives change Come whatever
随着时光转变  无论如何
We will still be Friends forever
我们还是朋友
Hey! Will you shut the fuck up and let me sing?
闭上你的鸟嘴  让我唱歌好吗
Hello?
哈罗
Hi, little guy. Look at you.
小家伙  你好
Little? I'm not little. I'm hung like a bull, lady. Check it out.
小  我才不小  我可大了
You ever seen a bird dick this big?
看过小鸟有如此巨根吗
- Too much for you, huh, baby?  - Yeah.
- 大吃一惊吧  - 是啊
All right. Step off then, sweet cheeks.
那就滚吧
Come back when you want some real loving.
有需要再来
OK.
好
Fucking tease.
去你的
Hello?
哈罗
Oh, I'm... I'm sorry, child. Did I frighten you, child?
抱歉  孩子  我吓坏你了
Oh, I'm sorry. Are you scared?
对不起  你吓到了
All right. I'll sing to you. God is in his holy temple
好吧  我唱歌给你听  上帝在她神圣的殿堂里
Better?
好多了
I'm here with Professor Oldman's group.
我是欧教授的学生
I'm Hanson. I'm the caretaker.
我是管家韩森
And what's your name, sweet child?
你叫什么名字
- I'm Cindy.  - Cindy.
- 我叫辛蒂  - 辛蒂
Oh, but the resemblance is striking.
长的真像
Look at the thin cheek bones and the same lips.
一样的削瘦双颊和双唇
Same... same eyes. Look at your hair.
一样的眼睛  还有你的头发
Oh, I'm sorry.
对不起
You've got the same nose. Tickle, tickle. Be-boop, be-boop on the nose.
还有一样的鼻子  呵呵
Shall I show you to your room?
我带你去房间吧好重
Oh! Oh, that's heavy. Whoo! That's heavy! I better use my strong hand.
我该用强壮的手来提
Oh! Clumsy.
哇  好多内裤
Oh! No, that's fine. Look, you got the panties... I can take care of it.
我能拿好
Look at... Oh, what you got here?
你的东西好多喔
Can't forget your toothbrush.
别忘了牙刷  晚上要用呢
Gonna need that for later.
以后会用
OK. Here we go. Follow me, child. Watch my bottom.
走  跟我来  跟着我的屁屁走
Coming through. Come on.
借过
Right this way. Here we are.
往这边  到了
So, um, do you live here by yourself?
你一个人住这
Well, yes. We've tried to rent it out...
对  我们想过要出租
but people don't seem to want to stay very long.
但好像没人敢住
Ha ha! Oh, there's old Mother Kane...
那是老夫人
and that's old Master Kane.
那是老先生
Who's that?
那是谁
That's Big Daddy Kane.
那是凯子主人
- Oh, he's cute.  - Oh, yeah.
- 它真可爱  - 是啊
That was the master's favorite toy.
那是凯子主人最喜欢的玩具
I don't know what it's doing out here.
真不知它怎么会在这里
I swear. Sometimes I think these toys have a mind of their own.
这些玩具有时好像是活的
Right this way.
这边
Oh, no, no, no. Not that room, sweetheart.
不  不是那间  小亲亲
No. That was the master's mistress's room.
那是主人情妇的房间
Yeah, he kind of was a little bit of a hornball.
他很色的
No. You go and stay right over here.
你住这间
This was the room that belonged to the love of his life...
这是他挚爱的房间
his wife, Caroline.
他的夫人  卡洛琳
I'll show it to you. Oh! Watch. My fanny's coming through.
我带你看  借我屁屁过一下
Watch it. Make room for fanny.
小心  屁屁要过来了
Oh, wow! It's beautiful.
真美
Well, thank you, child. You know, I have been working out.
谢谢你  我都有做运动
I've been doing my bun busters every day.
我天天都做提臀运动
I squeeze really tight, and then I let loose.
我用力缩紧  再放松
I squeeze really tight... and then let loose.
用力缩紧  再放松
Look at this.
你看
Caroline looked beautiful in that dress.
卡洛琳穿上那件可美呆了
In fact, she always looked her best.
其实  她一直是美若天仙
Do you know that she used to entertain...
她曾承欢皇室贵族
for royalty and common folk and...
和平民百姓
even the President of the United States.
甚至还有美国总统
Oh! Oh, don't be frightened, child. This is just Mr. Kittles.
别怕  这是猫老大
He was the master's favorite pet.
它是主人最喜欢的宠物
He's been in the family for generations.
它历经家族数代传承
Look at him. He hasn't aged a day.
看看它  还是像只小猫
All right, child, I think I'll take my leave.
好了  我想我该走了
You let me know if there's anything you need.
有任何需要直接来找我
Yes, and as you can see, Professor.I've taken care of everything.
教授  我已搞定一切
including medical supplies and blood storage. We want to be safe.
包括急救箱跟血浆  以防意外
Are these cameras all throughout the house?
这些监视器遍及各个角落吗
Yes, sir. I thought that would be best.
是的  我想这样最好
So if one of our little chickadees were to be taking a shower...
所以要是小妞去洗澡
- which button would I press to get a closeup?  - That one.
- 我该按哪个钮好看特写  - 那个
This one?
那个
Excuse me, Professor...
抱歉  教授
but your guests have begun to arrive...
你的客人已陆续抵达
and supper shall be served shortly.
晚餐马上就好了
OK. Thanks, handyman.
谢了  掌厨的
I'm actually the caretaker.
我是管家
Oh, aren't those cool new skates? Now, you be careful with those.
那是直排轮鞋吧  走路小心点
Don't want to fall and break something.
可别跌倒打破东西了
Oh, that's funny. That's real funny. Let me give you a hand.
真好笑  拍拍手
Well, that... that's awful kind of you.
你真好心
How about you give me a standing ovation?
干脆起立鼓掌算了
Why don't you lift me up?
你来扶我啊
Oh! OK. I see where you're going with this one.
好  我知道你想干嘛
You look familiar to me. Were you in "Stomp"?
你好面熟  跳过八家将吗
Hey, you can kiss my grits.
你去死吧
I think I'll be the bigger man now and walk away. Walk away.
好  我要走了  走了喔
- Um, I'll go and change for dinner.  - OK.
- 我要去准备晚餐  - 好的
I'll see you shortly.
等会见
Sounds good. I'll just run upstairs and jump into my jogging suit.
很好  我会立刻上楼
I'll be right down.
换上慢跑装后立刻下来
Hey there, little guy. How you doing?
小家伙  你好吗
Fuck off, four eyes.
滚开  四眼田鸡
I beg your pardon?
你说什么
I said, "Fuck off, four eyes."
我叫你滚开  四眼田鸡
- Oh, I ought to kick your ass.  - Hey! Hey! Hey!
- 你真欠揍  - 嗨  嗨  嗨
Relax, son. It's just a bird.
别这样  那只是一只鸟
Hello, birdie. Polly want a cracker?
小鸟  要不要吃　干啊
Polly wants your mama's sweet ass.
吃你老妈的屁屁啦
What did Polly say to me?
小鸟说什么
I said, "Polly wants your mama's sweet ass."
我说  小鸟要吃你老妈的屁屁
You don't be talking about my mama, son.
你不能这样叫我妈
You don't know my mama, son.
你又不认识她
Yeah, I know your mama. I fucked her last night.
我认识  我昨晚才玩过她
You want beef? I'll fuck you up!
想干架吗  你找死
Ooh! I'm shaking. I'm shaking.
好可怕  我好害怕
Now, fuck this. I'm gonna handle this shit like a gentleman.
妈的  我得文明一点
- Yo, hold my tooth, son.  - Yeah, come on, bitch.
- 来  拿好我的牙  - 来啊  爆炸头
You and that "Welcome Back, Kotter" haircut.
想跟我干架来啊
Want a piece of me? Come on. Bring it on.
你有种就来打啊
What you hard core? Gimme some.
你的核心吗  给我一些
- Bring it on bitch.  - No, no. What?
- 有种就来啊  - 不  不  什么
You gonna talk, son? Then do it.
你有种别只是讲  有种做啊
Let me out of here. Come on, pussy. Let me out of here. I'll fuck you up.
来啊  混蛋  放我出去  海扁你一顿
- Hi, guys.  - Hey.
- 大家好  - 你好
Hey.
你好
- Hey, Buddy.  - Hey, Cin.
- 嗨  巴迪  - 嗨  辛蒂
- How you doing?  - Open chest!
- 你最近好吗  - 胸前有空档
Come on. You got to be quicker than that, "A" cup.
你反应要快一点  A罩杯女
Oh! Oh!
喔  喔
- Hey, guys.  - Hey!
- 大家好  - 嗨
How you doing?
你最近好吗
Well, are you boys just gonna sit there with your mouths open
你们打算继续发呆流口水
or is someone gonna offer me a seat?
还是帮我弄个座位
I warmed it up for you. It's the best seat in the house.
我帮你暖好了  这是最棒的位子
Second best.
第二好的
Professor, is this the same house...
教授  这间房子
that a young girl was possessed by a demon...or something?
是不是曾有个小女孩被恶魔附身
Yes, it was reported but never substantiated.
是有这种报导  但未证实
All right. Well, uh... who'd like some appetizers?
谁要吃开胃菜
- That's what I like to hear.  - Hey, these buns look good.
- 我真高兴听到这些  - 这些面包看着真棒
Oh, yeah and they're so soft and warm.
是啊  又软又暖
-  Ray!  - Oh, I'm sorry. My bad.
- 小雷  - 抱歉  我的错
These are delicious.
真好吃
Thank you, my child. I made them by hand.
谢谢  我亲手做的
Here we go. I think the taters are just about done.
我想洋芋泥快好了
I'm just gonna give them one quick whisk here.
只需要再搅拌一下
OK, now. Dig in.
好了  自己来
All right. Now it's time for the turkey.
好  该切火鸡了
- Oh, what a beautiful bird.  - No! No, man!
- 粉嫩粉香的火鸡  - 不  不
Hey! Hey! Hey, man. Why don't you just relax...
你休息一下
and just let me do that for you?
让我来吧
- Yeah.  - Rest that little hand.
- 是啊  - 让小手休息一下吧
It's my pleasure, but what a nice young man to offer.
我很乐意  不过你真好心
- Let me give you a little pinch there. Come on.  - Fuck it!
- 让我捏捏你的小脸  - 噢  不
You know, a lot of people are kind of intimidated.
很多人很怕
about making a turkey, but really it's very simple.
料理火鸡  其实很简单
You just have to know the anatomy of a turkey...
你只要了解它的生理构造
and it's got, over here just the tiniest little stinkhole...
这里有个小小的屁眼
but it's big enough to get your hand right up inside it.
但它足以让你的手塞进去
I cook it with all the giblets...
把里面塞紧  我都把内脏一起煮
the penises and the ginies...
连蛋蛋也不放过
And now, a lot of people like to baste their turkeys... but I use this.
有人会在上面涂油  但我这样
I lick like that... and get into the little...
我用力舔
hiney hiney ho...
接着舔进它的小屁眼
That's nice and good. I don't know what the hell that is...
那没什么用  我不知它有啥用
but I'll lick it anyway. Up and down...
但我还是舔  上下舔
and then I like to get that right on there...
接着我对着它冲刺
Hiawatha!
上啊
And I got one of these. I'm gonna pull that off...
接着我再拔根毛放进去
and bam! That just kicks it up a little bit.
就更美味了
All right. I think that's almost...ready now.
等到我觉得差不多了
And then we bring it to the table.
就把它拿来餐桌旁
Mmm, good.
真香啊
All right. Who's ready for a wing?
好了  谁要吃鸡翅
Yours or the turkey's?
吃你的还是火鸡的
Well, I know what you'd like. How about a leg?
我知道你要吃什么  腿
How about two? Ha ha!
来两腿吧
How about I take these two legs and shove them right up your ass.
我拿那两只腿插你屁眼吧
all the way to the knee!
插给你死
Dwight. Dwight, relax.
歪头  冷静点
Hanson, may I ask you
韩森  请问你
is there something on the menu... that you haven't personally prepared?
菜单上有没有  不是你亲手准备的餐点
- Well, I ordered out the dessert.  - All right!
- 我叫了外卖甜点  - 太好了
Make room. Here comes the pie.
准备好  派来了
Who wants the first piece of that pie?
谁要吃第一片
Huh? I see you eyeing the first piece.
我看到你的眼神了
Oh, that's good.
很好
Mm mmm. Pass that down to her.
传给她
Thank you.
谢谢
That's nice.
很好
My germs. Ha ha ha!
我要
My germs! Ha ha ha!
Come play with me.
来玩
Come play.
Cindy... Cindy.
辛蒂  辛蒂
Who is it?
是谁
I want to help you, Cindy.
我想帮你  辛蒂
Who are you?
你是谁
You're in danger, Cindy. I want to help you.
你有危险  我想帮你
Help me how? Who's in danger?
怎么帮我  谁有危险
Check the music room.
去琴房看看
Where are you?
你在哪里
Check the fucking music room!
去那个烂琴房看看
Hey, Cindy, think fast! Ohh! Uhh! Aah!
辛蒂  反应快点
Dude, you suck! Ow.
你真逊
Buddy... about this friendship thing...
巴迪  关于做朋友的事
Yeah, I think it is so cool having a girl as a friend.
我觉得能有女的朋友很酷啊
That's just it, Buddy. I am a girl.
没错  我是女的
You can't be so rough with me.
你不能对我这么粗暴
Well, then what the hell are we supposed to do?
那我们该做什么
Gentle stuff. You know, like talking and...
温柔一点的事  像聊天
sharing secrets and past experiences. You know,
分享秘密和过去的经验
stuff like that.
就这些嘛
That sounds kind of gay.
真像是搞同性恋
I guess since you're a girl it's all right.
但你是女的  应该还好
-  Yeah. It'll be fine.  -  All right.
- 是啊  很好吗  - 好啊
Hey, listen. Will you come check something out with me?
要不要跟我去察看一下
Sure. We can practice our talking.
我们可以聊天
Yeah. Exactly.
没错
I want to tell you about this thing...
我想跟你说说
that happened to me when I was in high school.
我高中的事
Really? What happened?
发生了什么事
This hot Spanish chick's licking my nuts...
很呛的  和西班牙妞胡搞
- Buddy! No, no.  - This is the best part.
- 等等  - 这里最精彩
Oh, my God. Look.
天啊  你看
Oh, dude! Someone's on the rag! Shh!
真是  有人忘了垫卫生棉
They lead straight to the bookcase.
它往书架那边走
God.
天
Must be a secret study or something.
可能是个秘密基地
(凯阿修与情妇被谋杀)
It says Hugh Kane and his mistress were murdered in this house.
上面说凯阿修跟情妇在屋内遇害
Whoa. Check this out.
你看
This must be his wife.
这一定是他太太
Oh, my God. She looks just like you.
哇咧  她长的跟你好像
You think?
你真的这么想吗
- She's really beautiful.  - Yeah.
- 她真的好美  - 是啊
Well, actually, her hair doesn't have as many split ends as yours.
你头发的分叉比她多
and her skin isn't as oily as yours, either.
你的脸比较油
Also, sometimes your eyes get kind of squinty...
眼睛比较小
and you look like you might have Down Syndrome.
你看来像是得了唐氏症
- Other than that, though, the resemblance is uncanny.  - Really?
- 其他部份就很像了  - 是吗
Also, her tits are perfect.
还有  她的奶子比较大
They're not pointy or funny-looking like yours...
不像你的那么可笑
- or spaced too far apart.  - OK! Enough!
- 太外扩了  - 好了  够了
God.
天
Oh, my God, look at this.
天啊  快看
"Caroline." Must have been hers.
卡洛琳  这一定是她的
Oh, my God.
哦  天啊
All right. Let's get out of here. This place gives me the creeps.
快走吧  这里令人发毛
- OK. Grab the chest.  - Oh, thanks.
- 好吧  帮忙捧一下  - 谢谢了
- Buddy!  - What?
- 巴迪  - 什么
- I meant the chest.  - Right.
- 我是指箱子  - 好的
What the...
哇咧
(星期三)
(今天星期五)
Nice.
很好
Oh! OK! Hello! If I had known, I would have freshened up!
拜托  早知道我就会先洗澡
I wish you were freshened up, too. Get up there! Come on!
真希望你有先洗澡  上去
- Oh, you want this?  - Oh, yeah. Ooh, yeah.
- 这是你想要的  - 是的  是的
That's it, daddy. Take it like you want it. Give it to me! Give it to me!
够了  爸爸  尽情狂欢吧
Yeah! Come here!
不准跑
Bring it on! Kinky's my middle name, bitch!
来吧  我的外号叫种猪呢
That was the best that I've ever had.
这是我最棒的经验了
Oh. Mrs. Huey Kane. Doesn't that just have a ring to it?
凯太太  听起来不错呢
Ha ha! Mmm... baby? Where you going?
宝贝  你要去哪
Call me!
再联络哦
Let's do something freaky.
来点特别的吧
Hee hee! Like what, Ray?
什么特别的
I don't know.
我不知道
Why don't you talk dirty to me?
说点龌龊的话吧
I don't know what to say, Ray.
我不知道该说什么
Come on. Just make something up.
随便说啊
Oh, Ray, why do you make me so bad?
小雷  你让我变得好坏
Come on. Because you a bad girl.
你是个坏女孩
OK.
好吧
- I'm gonna work this.  - Yeah. Work it.
- 我要令你硬挺  - 来吧
I'm gonna make this mine.
我要占有它
Mmm. It's all yours. Oh, yeah.
全都是你的了
I'm gonna piss on your face...
我要尿在你脸上
and then I'm gonna fart in your mouth.
在你嘴里放屁
Yeah! And then I'm gonna shit on these walls, Ray! Ooh!
对  还要做蛋糕泄愤
Hey!
嘿
Too dirty?
太龌龊了
Hello?
是谁
Oh, hey, kitty, kitty. Hi, little fella.
小猫咪  你好啊
OK. OK. That's OK, cat.
好吧  猫咪
I think I know why you're mad, Mr. Cat.
我知道你为何这么生气
I didn't mean to go poopie in your litter box.
我不是故意在你砂盆里大便
Help! My pussy's gone crazy!
救命  猫老大发飙了
OK. You want a piece of me?
你想干架吗
Yeah! How do you like that, little pussy? Come on!
知道厉害了吧  贱猫
Yeah! Yeah! Come on!
来啊
Is that all you got? Huh? Come on!
你就只会这两下
Give me your best shot!
来点真本事吧
I'm telling you, Professor... it was possessed.
我告诉你  它被附身了
Theo, did you see this animal?
辣妹  你有看到它吗
No, I didn't. I heard all the commotion...
没有  我听到打斗声
but by the time I went in there. I guess it was gone.
我到的时候它已经不见了
Mm-hmm. What? So you think I did this to myself?
这总不会是我自己弄的吧
No. All I'm saying is that
我只是说
cats are known... to be very territorial animals...
猫很有领域观念
and it's likely that it did attack...
它是有可能攻击
but that doesn't mean it was possessed.
但那并不代表它被附身
Maybe you two should sleep together.
也许你们俩该睡一起
What are you getting at, Professor?
这话什么意思
I'm just saying that if indeed this cat did attack...
我只是想万一它再来攻击
it's less likely to come back if the two of you were...
它应该不会攻击你们的
let's say... together.
性灵合体
Oh, come on, it's college.
拜托  这是学术
It's time for you two to experiment.
你们俩这是做实验
I don't think we're gonna be getting much help here.
我想他是帮不上什么忙
Oh, on the contrary, actually...
刚好相反
I'd be more than happy to walk you through it.
我很乐意搓合你们
Come on, Cin. I'll make sure you get tucked in.
走吧  我送你去睡觉
Good idea. Don't forget to kiss each other good night.
很好  别忘了互吻道晚安
There's something going on in this house, Professor.
这屋内有鬼  教授
I'm not crazy! Aah!
我头壳没坏
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7,
一  二  三  四  五  六  七
8, 9, Brandon, 10, 11, Brandon, come on! Count with me!
八  九  十  十一  来吧  跟我一起数
Hey, you. Hee hee hee hee!
嘿  你好
Come here a minute. Ha ha ha ha!
进来一下
Come here. Ha ha ha ha!
快来
Peekaboo! Ha ha ha ha!
逮到你了
Come on, let's play!
想玩吗  来玩吧
This is a fun game, huh?
这游戏很有趣呢
Hey, what are you doing?
你干嘛
Uncle Ray-Ray's got a game.
雷叔叔有别的游戏
Hey, get your finger out of there.
把你的手指拿开
Tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle...
胳肢  胳肢  胳肢  胳肢
You want to play with Uncle Ray? Peekaboo! Ha ha ha ha!
跟我嘿咻嘿咻
Aah! Aah! Help!
救命啊
Oh, God!
天啊
Here's a little balloon animal. Da da da da da da da da da!
送你一个小汽球
(日记)
"I can't take living with him any longer.
我无法再跟他共处
"He's becoming a monster.
他成了一个怪兽
"I suspect he was having an affair.
我怀疑他在搞婚外情
"I believe he's sleeping with our baby-sitter Victoria.
他跟保母小薇有一腿
"It must be why he keeps her around...
所以他才雇她
"because we have no children."
但我们根本没小孩
Cindy. I want you to know what happened, Cindy.
辛蒂  我要你知道我的遭遇
Hello, Cindy.
你好  辛蒂
Hello, Professor.
你好  教授
I take it you're not mad at me anymore.
你不生我的气了
I wouldn't go that far, Professor.
怎么会呢  教授
Why don't you just relax?
你放轻松点嘛
I think she's starting to suspect something.
她好像起疑心了
Who?
谁
Your wife.
你老婆啊
- Oh, my God. It happened right here.  - What?
- 天啊  就是在这里发生的  - 什么
She came home.
她回到家
She saw them!
看到了他们
Saw who?
看到谁
I was in my room reading her journal.
我本来在她房里看她的日记
Then I found this dress in the closet.
接着我在柜子里找到这件衣服
That's all I remember.
我只记得这么多了
What about you, Ray?
你呢  小雷
Oh, I bought mine on Friday. I just came down to get a banana.
我是来找吃的  洋装是周五买的
Shit is hot, right?
够美吧
You're a nice little plant.
晚安  小树苗
You drink all this little water up...
喝光水水
so you can grow up to be a nice strong chron plant. Yes. Yes.
长成又高又壮的大麻树
And then you'll be smoked by all the rappers and make them do
我就能把你卷起来
a whole lot of dumb shit that fuck up their careers.
然后毁了你的前途
Yes you will.
你会的
Night-night, baby.
晚安  宝贝
(牙仙子)
I'm gonna rob that bitch tonight.
我今晚要抢牙仙子
Lockdown Records presents A Hip-Hop Christmas.
霉龟唱片推出嘻哈圣诞专辑
You'll get such classics... As "Santa Claus Is Coming on Moms..."
收录经典  圣诞公公跟我老母
- That's the shit son!  - "I'm Dreaming of a White Woman"
- 真是太爽了  - 我正梦到一个白人女人
and who could forget "Frosty the Dopeman"?
还有  雪人怎么不贱了
And how about "All I want for Christmas... Is the Charges Dropped..."
圣诞叫床声  淫色圣诞
"Deez Nuts Roasting On an Open Fire..."
我不要在牢里过圣诞
"A Sleigh Ride In My '64..." "Ante Up, Bitch, It's Christmas..."
一路爽叮当
- and many more!  - Yo, I'm gonna buy that shit, son!
- 还有很多好听的酷歌  - 我要买这张
Just $ 19.95...
只要19块95
I'm sorry! I didn't mean to smoke your relatives! Please! No!
我不是有意抽你亲戚的
I didn't do it by myself! Whitney and Bobby helped me! Please! Help me!
都是惠妮跟巴比布朗教我的
Wait! No! Please!
等等
Oh! Oh, shit, son!
靠
Oh, shit!
哦  靠
Oh, my God!
哦  天啊
Aah! Oh, shit! I smell something burning!
有东西烧焦了
Oh, stop! It's me!
靠  就是我嘛
I got an idea!
我有个主意
- Oh, wait a second!  - Hold on, Shorty!
- 等一等  - 撑着点  矮子
Don't rescue me yet. I'm getting high as a motherfucker!
先别救我  这样满high的
Toke, toke, toke, toke! Take it to the head! Take it to the head!
抽吧  用力抽
Oh, you take it like a bitch.
你象个婊子
Put the Shorty down and I'll give you Funyons and Cheetos.
把矮子放下  我就给你洋芋片
Oh, shit!
靠
This shit burns more than a perm!
这玩意烧的比烫头发还快
There's a whole lot of freaky shit going on in this house.
这屋子有鬼
There's more to this story than the Professor told us.
教授没有说实话
Last night, I found a secret room...
我昨晚发现一个密室
and I found all these newspaper clippings about Hugh Kane.
找到这些跟凯阿修有关的剪报
He was a really evil man.
他很邪恶
And I found a picture of his wife.
我还找到一张他老婆的照片
Oh, my God! She looks just like you.
哇靠  她跟你好像
You think?
真的
She doesn't have as many split ends and her skin's not as oily as yours.
你头发的分叉比她多  你的脸比较油
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Sometimes you do this little squinty thing with your eyes.
是啊  还有你的眼睛小
It looks like you got Down Syndrome or something.
看来像是得了唐氏症
Oh, yeah, y'all look just alike except she got some perfect boobs.
你们真的很像  但她奶子较大
and yours look like them old orangutan titties.
你的像红毛猩猩一样瘪
I'll put you in the full nelson and lick them. Ha ha h ha!
要后仰才能露出来
OK! Enough!
好了  够了
Anyway, I think she killed him and now he wants me.
我想是她杀了他  而他想找我
Yeah. Right, bitch.
是啊  贱货
Morning, Dwight. Let me help you.
早安  歪头  我来帮你
I don't need your help. I can do it myself.
我不需要帮忙  我可以自己来
OK. Professor, uh, we need to talk.
教授  我们需要谈谈
What is it, Dwight?
什么事
I think you should consider cutting the experiment short. What?
我想你该考虑中断实验
This poltergeist is growing increasingly more violent.
屋里的鬼越来越残暴了
I think we're all in danger here and I've got to put my foot down.
我们有危险  我得脚踏实地
and stand up for what I believe in...
站出来
and say that we've got to pull the plug.
阻止这场实验
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, Dwight. I say when we pull the plug.
歪头  这得由我来决定
We are on the verge of greatness...
我们就快成功了
and I am this close to getting laid.
我也快搞上辣妹了
Now, the bus arrives on Monday. No one leaves till then.
礼拜一前  谁也不能走
Here are the keys to the gate.No one gets access to them.
这是大门的钥匙  不准任何人走
Yes, sir.
好的  教授
Guys, I think the Professor's up to something.
各位  我想教授别有阴谋
I heard Dwight tell the Professor...
我听到歪头说
there could be a poltergeist in the house...
这屋内有恶鬼
and that we could all be in danger!
我们可能都有危险
Oh, no, son! Not a poltergeist!
不会吧  不要恶鬼
What's a poltergeist?
什么是饿鬼
I'm getting out of here.
我要走了
No. We can't go anywhere. The gates are locked.
不行  大门锁起来了
Dwight's the only one who has the keys.
只有歪头有钥匙
- Baby, get my Vaseline.  - I'll handle...
- 拿凡士林来  - 我来
Get my Vaseline, a banana, and some duct tape.
拿凡士林  香蕉跟胶带来
I'm gonna break his legs.
我要打断他的腿
I'm gonna fuck that little cripple up!
给他阿鲁巴
Guys, just give me five minutes alone with him.I'll get the keys.
给我五分钟  我可以拿到钥匙
Hello, Dwight.
你好  歪头
Hi, Theo.
你好  辣妹
What you working on?
你在干嘛
Uh, just a little experiment.
只是个小实验
Oh. Work, work, work.Is that all you ever do?
工作  工作  怎么老是工作
Well, there's a lot riding on this project.
这个计划有很多变数
You know, the Professor might have everyone else fooled but
教授把大家耍的团团转
I know who the real brains behind this operation is.
但我知道谁才是真正的天才
Oh, yeah? You do, huh?
真的
Mm-hmm. That's what turns me on about you.
我对你着迷不已
You're so smart. And those sexy eyes.
你好聪明  眼睛又性感
- Why don't I put some music on, huh?  - Yeah. Music.
- 放点音乐吧  - 好啊
You know, Dwight...
歪头
I hear you're the only one who has the keys to the gate.
听说你有大门钥匙
Ha. That's true. It is. I'm... Correct.
是啊  没错
What if...
如果
I wanted to borrow those keys?
我想借钥匙呢
Oh, dear sweet God in Heaven.
亲爱的上帝
I... yaaa, I can't.
不可以
- Oh, come on. Yes, you can, baby.  - No.
- 你可以的  宝贝  - 不
Please? I mean...
求求你
Look. You help me by giving me the keys...
你把钥匙给我
and I'll help by giving you...
我就帮你
Hey, wait, wait, wait! Whoa!
等等
Hey, I don't need your help, OK, lady?
我不需要帮忙
I can do it myself.
我可以自己来
Hey, look!
看
I'm tossing my own salad!
我折腾自己的沙拉
So this is your secret room.
原来这就是你的密室
Well...
好吧
this just isn't gonna work now, is it?
这样下去不行的
Oh, Professor.
教授
Come over here.
过来
This way, you big hunk.
这边  大帅哥
Have we met?
我们见过吗
Follow me.
来  等你喔
Are you playing a little game?Where are you?
别闹了  你在哪里
Come here, baby.
这里  宝贝
No!
不
- Is everybody here?  - Yeah.
- 大家都到了吗  - 是的
All right. Let's go.
好的  我们走
Oh! Oh, shit, son!
妈的
He's not gonna let us out of here! He's gonna kill us!
他不会让我们走  他要杀我们
Oh, look. A rocket scientist.
快看  有丑女
All right. Quick. Everybody to the laboratory.
大家快点  到实验室去
Move! Come on! Hurry up!
走 快跑
You all are fucked!
你们死定了
Lock the door.
锁门
- OK. We have to destroy it.  - That's great.
- 我们得摧毁它  - 好的
How are we gonna destroy what we can't see?
我们又看不见它  怎么摧毁它
I got it! We'll shave off our pubic hairs...
有了  我们把毛剃光
and wear the shampoo for two weeks!
再涂上头虱药
No. Listen. Listen. We're gonna use these guns.
听着  我们要用这些枪
They emit a bolt of concentrated energy
它们能放射能源弹
which can damage the ectoplasmic cells and destroy the ghost.
破坏灵体  摧毁鬼魂
Now, there's no more ammunition. Conserve it. Use it wisely.
弹药有限  别乱开枪
Shut up.
闭嘴
- Hey! Hey! Hey! Conserve your ammunition.  - My bad.
- 节约弹药  - 我错了
All right. Now, the only way...
对不起
we're gonna be able to track these ghosts is
唯一能搜寻
if we're all wearing one of these.
鬼魂的办法
These are thermo goggles. They work on the principle of body heat.
就是戴上这些感热护目镜
They're so powerful, they can detect...
它能感测体温  功能强大
where any bodily fluids have been...
甚至能测得残留体液
even if they've been wiped clean.
纵使你早已擦干净
What?
怎么
Are my glasses crooked?
有问题吗
Now listen, that ghost may be invisible...
听着  鬼也许无形
but we have the advantage of being armed...
但我们有高科技武器
with the most sophisticated high-tech equipment known to man.
能用来对付它
How do we stay in touch with each other? Do we have some walkie-talkies?
我们怎么联系  有对讲机吗
No. We have these.
用这些
Those is Dixie cups.
这是纸杯耶
Well, we kind of ran short of funds after the guns and the goggles.
护目镜跟能源枪花光了经费
All right. Now let's split up.
好  我们分开行动
Now wait a minute! Hold up!
给我站住
How come every time some scary shit happens...
怎么每次发生
that we need to stick together...
什么恐怖的事
you white people always say, "Let's split up"?
你们白人就爱叫人散开
She's right. We should stick together.
她说的对  团结就是力量
Yes! That's what I'm saying!
没错
She's right. OK. You three, follow me.
好  你们三个  跟我走
Ain't that a bitch?
哇咧
We're gonna die, y'all.
我们死定了
Ah. Did you hear that?
听见吗
Hell, yeah.
听见了
Oh! Where's Shorty?
矮子呢
I don't know. Shorty!
不知道  矮子
Shorty!
矮子
Damn.
该死
All right. You wait right here. I'll be right back.
你在这等着  我马上回来
- OK.  - All right.
- 好的  - 没事的
What is this?
这里是干嘛的
I don't know.
不知道
Looks like the furnace room.
大概是暖炉吧
- All right. Let's go.  - No, wait.
- 走吧  - 不  等等
In that newspaper article,
剪报上写凯阿修就是
it said that Hugh Kane was killed in the furnace.
在暖炉遇害
Oh, wow. Look at this. There's so many ashes, Buddy.
你看  好多灰
(大选变天)
- What are you doing?  - Hold it.
- 你在干嘛  - 慢着
- Let's split up. I'll meet you on the other end.  - OK.
- 我们散开  到那端会合  - 好的
Wait. Good luck.
等等  祝你好运
I love you!
我爱你
(杀她)
- Oh, Shorty!  - Cindy!
- 矮子  - 辛蒂
There's a monster chasing me. What are we gonna do?
有怪物追我  我们该怎么办
- I got it!  - Yeah?
- 有了  - 什么
Shorty!
矮子
Damn. Why does the little bitch got to bring that shit over here?
靠  那贱货干嘛把它引到这里
OK. Well, maybe she won't see me.
也许她不会看到我
Somebody help me! Brenda!
救命啊  小兰
Shit, she saw me. OK. OK.
妈的  她看到我了  好吧
Thank you, Lord!
感谢上帝
OK. Now let that shit just, just mutilate her white ass and leave.
让那怪物把她大卸八块吧
Damn, bitch, please die!
妈的  快死吧
Oh, my God, Brenda! We're gonna die!
天啊  小兰  我们死定了
It would have just been you if you had just shut the fuck up!
都是你乱叫拖我下水
It's coming!
它来了
What is it?
它是什么
Is it a monster? Is it a monster?
它是怪物吗  它是怪物吗
Cindy? This is a skeleton. This is bones.
这只是骷髅  骨头罢了
Would you run from Calista Flockhart?
得了厌食症的下场
Shut your ass up.
闭上你的鸟嘴
Look. He crazy now.
它发疯了
I'm sorry, Mr. Skeleton. Here.
骷髅先生  在这里
Ha! Gotcha! Psych!
哈  上当了
Have a nice trip. Ha ha ha!
一路顺风
Hey, girl, I got an idea. Come on.
我有个主意  过来
Ha ha. Very funny. Whoo!
真有趣
Now get on out of here!
给我滚
Somebody gonna catch an ass-whupping when I come back.
等我回来就有人要倒大霉了
Oh, Brenda, you are so brave.
小兰  你好勇敢
You know, you really are my best friend, Cindy.
你真是我的好朋友
You guys OK?
你们没事吧
- Yeah.  - Please.
- 没事  - 当然啦
It takes more than a little bag of bones to scare me.
它根本吓不倒我
- Wedgie!  - Ha ha ha!
- 大内裤  - 啊啊啊
The ghost has Buddy!
鬼抓了巴迪
My ass!
我的屁屁
- Brenda, do something!  - OK!
- 想想办法  小兰  - 好
I thought I was your best friend.
我以为我是你最好的朋友
Was. I'm gonna miss you, girl!
那是过去式了  我会想你的
Get my gun!
我的枪
Are you OK?
你还好吧
Oh, my God, you're bleeding.
你流血了
Come on. I think there's a first-aid kit in the lab. Come on.
来  实验室有急救箱
Huey, baby, where are you?
宝贝小阿修  你在哪里
My love? Are you there?
爱人  你在那里吗
Huey? Baby! Baby, I got to talk to you.
小阿修  我要跟你谈谈
- No. Go away!  - Baby?
- 不  滚开  - 宝贝
Get away from me!
别来烦我
Come on, baby. We can work this out.
来嘛  宝贝  我们谈谈
I mean, if we just stick together, no one can hurt us, my love.
相爱相守  谁能伤害我们
It was just a booty call!
那只是一夜情
Why won't you talk to me?
你干嘛不跟我谈
Because you gave me crabs.
因为你给我螃蟹
You are the weakest link. Good-bye!
你真没用  再见
Hey. How you doing? Ha ha ha!
你好吗
No, no. No kissing. No kissing.
不亲嘴  不亲嘴
No. Leave this on. Leave this on.
戴着这个
You look beautiful just like that. Yeah. Yeah. Oh! Oh!
你就美呆了
No, no, no.
不不不
Don't fuck it up.
别毁了这一切
I've been thinking about this whole friendship thing.
我仔细思考我们之间的友谊
I've never had a friend who cared for me the way you do.
从未有朋友这么关心我
I mean, there's Ray...
小雷也关心我
but he cares for me in a different way...
但那不一样
you know, like bringing me flowers...
他送花给我
and running my bath water.
帮我放洗澡水
And there's nights when I wake up screaming,
当我夜里被恶梦惊醒
and I look over, and Ray's in my bed holding me.
小雷会在床上搂着我
Anyway seeing as how tonight may be our last night together...
总之  今晚也许是最后一夜了
I was thinking...
我在想
That we should take our friendship a little bit further.
我们该更深入交往
- Yes.  - Oh, Buddy!
- 没错  - 噢  巴迪
I was thinking the exact same thing.
我也这么想
This might be our last night alive...
这可能是我们的最后一夜
and I want to take full advantage of it.
我想享受一切
I was thinking the same thing!
我也这么想
- I want to be able to act out our innermost fantasies.  - Oh, great.
- 我要满足我们最深切的幻想  - 太棒了
- Like I've always wanted to walk on the moon.  - Huh?
- 像我一直都想到月球上漫步  - 什么
What about you, Buddy? What do you want to do?
你呢  你想做什么
He's in here. Oh!
鬼来啦
Oh, my God. He locked us in.
天啊  他把我们锁起来了
You should call for help.
你该找人援助
Hello! Hello. Can you hear me?
呼叫  有人听见吗
Come in! Come in! Copy! Do you copy me?
请说  有人听见吗
We have a situation here! Breaker!
这里有状况  呼叫
Oh, my God. They can't hear me!
他们听不见
Must be these walls or something.
应该是墙隔住了
OK. All right.
好吧
- You stay down here. I'll go check upstairs.  - OK.
- 你待在这  我上楼去看看  - 好的
- Do you need help or...  - No!
- 需要帮忙吗  - 不
OK.
好吧
What do I look like to you?
你想干嘛
Just trying to be nice.
表示友好
Cover me!
掩护我
What do you want me to do?
什么
Cover me!
掩护我
Not literally. I'm serpentining!
用火力掩护  我这是S形前进
They taught me that Merchant marines. Two years.
这是我当佣兵两年学会的
- Spent two years on my belly in Danang.  - Yeah.
- 我在越南匍匐前进了两年  - 这样啊
Look. Look. Look what the cripple's doing.
哇  看那个残废在做什么
Oh, shit.
哇靠
Look, I know you're proud. Just let me help you up.
我了解你的自尊  让我帮你吧
Step it back, candy pants!
退后  臭娘们
Fine.
好吧
Oh, what are we gonna do? I'm cold.
我们该怎么办  我好冷
I can't feel my body, I'm so cold.
我失去知觉了  好冷
Buddy, can you feel this?
这样有感觉吗
No.
没
Try a little higher.
没  再上面一点
What about that?
这样呢
Mm-mmm. Keep rubbing.
继续摩擦
Oh, Buddy, I don't think I'm re...
拜托  我没准
Cindy, please! It's a matter of life and death.
这是生离死别的关头
I'm asking you... in the name of love.
我以爱为名请求你
OK, Buddy. In the name of love.
好  巴迪  一切为爱
Oh, Cindy... I don't know how much longer I can hold on.
辛蒂  我快撑不住了
Don't you say your good-byes.
不许你就这样走掉
You're gonna get out of here...
你一定能出去的
and you're gonna go on and you're gonna have lots of little babies.
你以后也会子孙满堂
- And you're gonna die an old man.  - Old man.
- 你也必将安享天年  - 安享天年
- Warm in his bed.  - Warm in his bed.
- 在家寿终  - 在家寿终
- Not here!  - No.
- 不是在这  - 不是
- Not like this!  - Amen.
- 不是这样  - 一个男人
- Do you understand me?  -  Oh, yeah.
- 你懂吗  - 噢  我懂
Coming to this house was the best thing that ever happened to me.
被关在此是我此生最美好的事
Oh, me, too.
我也是
And for that, I am so thankful.
因此  我心存感激
Never! I'll never let go!
我永不放手
- I feel weak.  - Buddy!
- 我好虚弱  - 巴迪
- I'm com...  - Come back!
- 我要去了  - 回过神来啊
All right, Dwight Hartman.
好  歪头
It's your time to shine. All right. Come on.
该你上场表现了
Come on, Kane.
来吧  姓凯的
Show yourself!
出来
Look. I don't even need my thermal goggles.
我不需要什么感热护目镜
That's right, mother...
就这样
Hey, Kane, you hungry? How about a little snack of this?
姓凯的  饿吗  该吃点心了
Gotcha!
逮到你了
I know what you're thinking.
我知你在想什么
Did I fire 3 shots or 117?
我弹药够吗还是
Well, do you feel lucky, punk?
你觉得你运气够好吗
Do you... feel lucky? Do you feel lucky, punk?
你觉得自己够走运吗
Shoot me, motherfucker!
开枪吧  猪头
OK. Fine.
好
Make your best move, ass bite.
动手吧  废人
(风火轮)
Help! Help!
救命  救命
Here. Take my hand.
来  抓住我的手
Come on. You're gonna fall unless you take my hand.
再不抓你就会掉下去了
No. Give me your other hand.
不  伸出你另一支手
No. My other hand isn't strong enough.
另一支手没力
You take my little hand.
抓我的小手
No! Get it away from me!
不  别碰我
Take it! Take my hand!
快  抓住我的手
No. No. Why me? No. Come on. No.
不  为何找上我
I've served you well. Don't you do this to me.
我忠心耿耿
No, please. Please, no. Ple-ple-ple... Aah!
别这么对我
OK, Buddy. It's time for us to get out of here.
巴迪  我们该离开了
Roger. Roger. Come in, Roger.
收到  请说
Ray, this is Cindy.
我是辛蒂
I don't want to talk to Cindy.I want to talk to Roger.
我不要你  我要找罗杰
Roger, where you at, man? Quit fucking around.
罗杰  你在哪  别再混了
Ray, listen. The ghost is close. He almost got us. Buddy's hurt.
听着  恶鬼怪发飙  巴迪受伤了
- What's your location?  - I'm right behind you.
- 你在哪里  - 就在你后面
Ray, thank God. OK. Where's Shorty?
感谢上帝  矮子呢
I don't... I don't know. He was here just a minute ago.
不知  他刚才还在的
Listen, you go help Buddy in the lab.
好  你去帮巴迪
- I'll go check upstairs.  - All right.
- 我去楼上看看  - 好的
Mmm. That smells good.
真香
Hello, Cindy.
你好  辛蒂
Say heloo to Cindy, Shorty.
矮子  跟辛蒂打招呼
Heloo... Cindy.
你好  辛蒂
Shorty, are you OK? Talk to me!
你没事吧  说话啊
Morphine? Chloroform? Horse tranquilizers? You drugged him!
吗啡  摇头丸  你对他下药
I did not. That's all his stuff.
我没有  那都是他的
All right, Shorty. Who's ready for the main course?
好了  矮子  谁要吃大餐
Me! Me.
我  我
Oh, Hanson, please. No. Oh.
韩森  不要
- What the fuck?  - Beetlejuice in the house.
- 搞屁啊  - 吸毒的小孩
This is your brains on drugs. Hee!
脑子就长这样
Shorty!
矮子
Got me.
真是酷毙了
Cindy, what's going on?
怎么了
It's Hanson. He's possessed. Let's get him.
韩森被附身了  快阻止他
Angel style!
娇娃出动
You OK, Dwight?
你没事吧
I... I can't feel my legs.
我的脚失去知觉了
Aah! I can't feel my legs!
我感觉不到我的脚
You never could.
废话
You stay out of this, all right?
你给我闭嘴
- Now listen. You get the others and meet us upstairs. All right?  - OK.
- 通知大家到楼上会合  - 好的
You stay here. Ray-Ray, I need your help. Give me your belt.
小雷你留下  皮带给我
The crane.
鹤形拳
The crouching tiger.
卧虎拳
The drunken monkey.
醉猴拳
The mad cow.
狂牛拳
Motherfucker! Moo!
有胆来啊  哞
The camel toe.
骆驼腿
Get the hell out of there, guys! Come on!
我们走吧  快点
Ray, give me a 180.
向后转
OK. Listen. Someone has to go and lure him onto that platform.
好  得有人到平台上诱他上钩
All right. I'll go.
我去
- Cindy, let me...  - No, Buddy!
- 辛蒂  让我  - 不  巴迪
I'm the one he wants.
他要的是我
Actually, I was saying... let me have your computer if you die.
我是想万一你死了  电脑给我
- OK. But as soon as he gets there, you have to get off.  - OK.
- 他一上去你就赶快下来  - 好的
All right. 180 me.
向后转
Hugh Kane, it's me you want! Come get me!
凯阿修  你要的是我  来吧
I'm not afraid anymore! Show yourself!
我不怕了  出来吧
Dwight, he's here. Do something.
歪头  快动手
I can't. She's still on the platform.
不行  她还在上面
If I throw the switch, she'll die.
如果我打开开关  她会死的
Cindy, get out of there! You'll get killed!
辛蒂  快走  你会死的
Move out of the way! I'll get her!
让开  我去救她
Why is he running so slow?
他怎么跑这么慢
Ray! Run faster!
小雷  快点
OK!
好
Throw the switch!
打开开关
Now you will be mine forever!
你是我的了  永远
Ray, you saved me. Are you OK?
小雷  你救了我  你还好吧
I'm fine. I broke my fall.
没事  后面有垫背的
Hey, y'all. What's going on?
发生什么事情了
Shorty, you made it. You're alive!
矮子  你没死  我们成功了
(二个月后)
Yeah. It was traumatic.It really was...
那真是一场惊魂记
and it's taking me a while to get over it, but, you know.
我得花点时间复原
now that we're out of the house and back in school...
我们已出来  重返学校
I just know that everything's gonna be OK.
我知道一切都会好转
Oh, God, will you shut the fuck up?
天啊  闭上你的鸟嘴吧
Why couldn't you have just left me there to die?
你干嘛不让我死了算了
Give me a fucking rope. I'll hang myself.
给我绳子  我要上吊
Here I go. I'm hanging myself.
好了  我上吊了
Hello? Oh, hi, Dad. Are you having fun on your vacation?
爸  你玩得愉快吧
Oh, no. Birds are very clean animals. He's no trouble at all.
不  鸟很爱干净的  没问题
Goddamn it! What the fuck did you put in this birdseed?
哇靠  你在鸟食里放了什么
Oh, Dad, Buddy's here. I got to go. OK. I love you. Bye.
巴迪来了  我要挂了  拜
God, that was a big one.
哇  好大一摊
Hey, Buddy!
巴迪
Surprise.Open chest!
惊喜  胸前有空档
Oh! You got to be quicker than that, pencil dick.
你得快点  小根男
Come on.
来吧
Hey, look out. A bee.
小心蜜蜂
Buddy, I've never had anyone be so protective of me before.
你是这世上最保护我的人了
That's what your man's supposed to do.
做你的男人就该这样
Two hot dogs.
两根热狗
Buddy, get him!
巴迪  抓住他
Buddy? Buddy?
巴迪  巴迪
I've come back for you.
我回来找你了
No! This can't be happening!
不  这是不可能的
It is happening. Now we're gonna be together forever.
没错  我们将厮守终身了
Nooooo!
不
Yes!
好耶
Did you hear something?
你听见了吗
No. I didn't hear nothing.
不  我什么也没听见